                                                                                                    
                                                                                ;;ii;;                
                                                                          ::iiiiiiii                  
                                                                    ..iiii;;..  ii..                  
                                                                ..ttii..      ii::                    
      ..;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;iiiiii..    ::;;                      
    ..::                                                    ..;;ii;;..      ii..                      
  ..::                                                ::;;ii;;..            ;;;;..................    
..::                                            ..;;ii::..                    ..iiiiffffffffffffjjii  
::..        http://infinitymugenteam.com/     ..,,ii....                        ..iifffffffffffffftt..
  ::..                                              ..;;;;....              ..;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;;    
    ::..         Share & Create                           ,,;;;;....        ii..                      
      ::......................................................;;iiii;;..    ;;,,                      
        ........................................................,,iiii        ii..                    
                                                                  ,,;;ii;;..  ..ii                    
                                                                        ;;iiii,,;;;;                  
                                                                              ;;iitt..                
                                                                                  ;;;; 


----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
-------------------------- Skull man - Robot Master Mayhem Edition --------------------------
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Skull man - 1-30-2020
Sprited By: Manic
Coding:  Mistah Jorge, O Ilusionista, AJrenaln
Voices: Shadowken
http://www.infinitymugenteam.com/ 

--------------------------------------

History:  
A balanced out war robot. He was only taught about fighting and nothing else.
"Let's fight, let's fight..."

--------------------------------------

Credits/Special Thanks to:

AJrenaln		For working on the initial verion of Skull man.
O Ilusionista		For fixing up and adding polish to the character.
Mistah Jorge		Current coder.
IMT/Acey/Chaotic:	Thanks for the Robot Master Mayhem character template and the custom edits included in the template.
Everyone Else:		Yea you guys left me comments and cheered me on which keeps me spriting.


----------
Button Notation
----------

UB  U  UF
  \ | /    LP  MP  HP
B-  X  -F
  / | \    LK  MK  HK
DB  D  DF

U: Up
D: Down
B: Back
F: Forward

P:  Punch
LP: Low Punch
MP: Medium Punch
HP: High punch
PP: Any combination of two punch buttons at same time
K:  Kick
LK: Low Kick
MK: Medium Kick
HK: Hard Kick
KK: Any combination of two kick buttons at same time

QCF: Quarter-circle Forward (D, DF, F)
QCB: Quarter-circle Backward (D, DB, B)
DP: Dragon-Punch (F, D, DF)
DPB: Dragon-Punch Backward (B, D, DB)


----------
Move list (details and/or tips of each move listed here are further down bellow, trust me, you better read up a bit)
----------

Special moves:
----------
Power Shot:			QCF + P (AIR OK)
(Use power set selected):	QCF + K
Skull Barrier:			QCB + K
Teleport:			QCB + P
Invivibility toggle: 		F, B, F + P/K

Power Sets:
----------
(In summary, 6 selectable special moves that will occupy "QFC + K" input, you select which power set you want to use mid-rounds with D, D + any normal button)
#1 - Haunt:			D, D + LK (AIR OK)
#2 - Rib Spikes:		D, D + MK (AIR OK)
#3 - Skull missile:		D, D + HK (AIR OK)
#4 - Homming missile:		D, D + LP
#5 - Skull joe:			D, D + MP
#6 - Skeletal sweep:		D, D + HP	

Hyper Moves:
----------
Dual uzis (LVL 1):		QCF + PP
Laughing skulls (LVL 1):	QCF + KK
Skull bot  LVL 3:		QFB + PP

----------
Move details
----------

- Before anything else it's important to point out Skull man's main gimmick revolving Skull barrier, as you CAN'T use Power sets while the barrier is in effect,
	more details in Skull barrier's description;
- That's it, you don't really need to read up the rest, but you kind of should tho.

Power Shot
----------
- Your standard zoning tool, works generally well, doesn't drain your health like Haunt;
- LP has fastest start up, but has the slowest recovery;
- MP has a slower startup, but faster recovery;
- HP is on par with MP regarding frame data, but it's shoot diagonally, has also more damage than the other button variations;
- MP and HP are good follow ups on standing hard punch, dash close to the opponent fast enough to continue a combo
	(ex: LP, HP, QCF + MP, HK, (continue with whatever works));
- AIR Power shot has no variations what-so-ever, mostly used as an combo ender;
- AIR power shot sends skull man "flying backwards" a bit.

Skull Barrier
----------
- Exclusively a defensive tool, making you completly invincible against up to 8 projectiles hits;
- However, you are still vulnerable against everything else, as in melee and throws;
- Another trade of is that you can't use any power set at all, cripling skull man's offensive gameplay, consider which situations are better
	to just use power sets instead;
- You can still use the rest of the Skull man's move set freely;
- Going invisible or teleporting destroys the barrier on the spot;
- Activating the skull barrier turns off invisibility;
- If needed, you can destroy your barrier at will by inputting QCB + K again;

Teleport
----------
- Basic teleport;
- Teleport's start up is instant when skull man's already invisible;
- Any teleport destroy Skull barrier on startup;
- LP teleports skull man backwards a bit;
- MP teleports around the same distance of LP, but forwards;
- HP teleports around double the distance forwards.

Invisibility
----------
- Skull man becomes invisible, nuff said;
- Unfortunatly, there's no way to code for the CPU NOT to know your position, real players will have to guess tho;
- However, Skull man slowly charges power (your power meter) while invisible, as a way to encourage this special move's usage;
- Being hit or guarding attacks turns skull man's invisibility off;
- Your projectiles and effects (like jump dust) aren't invisible, use this to track down where you are if you're lost;
- You can toggle off invisibility by inputting F, B, F + P/K (any attack button) again;
- The animations are the same of the teleport one, mix other players if they think you're teleporting (CPU's won't obviously fall for it);

Haunt
----------
- A projectile move, with it's own gimmicks, skull man shoots out a ghostly skull, it costs some health;
- If the skull hits tho, Skull man gains his health back with a small bonus, it's risk-reward isn't too costly nor too rewarding;
- This projectile's damage is considerably weaker than power shot;
- The good stuff with this move is the combo opportunities it gives:
* Lk flies downwards before going straight, it trips opponents if the skull is close enough to the ground;
* MK flies straight horizontally, if it hits the opponent it will make him turn his back on you;
* HK flies upwards before going straight, if it hits airborn opponents it will make them flip backwards;
- The skull's variations on the air are the same as the ground, you can trip opponents if your close enough to the floor (Tiger knee!);
- You can attack after shooting a skull on the air, unlike power shot.

Rib spikes
----------
- A hard to hit move, it's hitboxes are in the edges of the spikes;
- Strong damage wise;
- Each variation of this move has it's own range and damage;
- Upper spikes makes opponents fly up, else skull man sends opponents flying away from him;
- Better off for following up standing Hard P with QCB + MK and standing Hard Kick with QCB + HK;

Skull missile
----------
- Projectiles that are stand by for a short while before going forwards;
- Each variation has it's own stand by time before going forwards;
- Hommes in vertically;
- Can shoot up to two missiles on the screen;

Skeletal sweep
----------
- Summons a skeleton minnion that hits low (sweep) while rising;
- Skeleton's position dependends on wich button used:
* LK closest to skull man;
* Hk is the farthest.